

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

My name is Armando Tinoco.

I am a back-end Web Developer and Electronics technologist with great ability to design and develop timely strategies, I have experience in Python, JavaScript, AWS and Node js, with knowledge of agile SCRUM methodologies and great analytical skills to solve problems effectively.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

--Backend developer. -

Databases.

- -MYSQL.
- -ORACLE
- -MONGODB
- Python
- Node JS.
- Jest
- Docker
- POO.
- Flask.
- · APIS tipo REST.
- AWS
- ANSIBLE
- SCRUM

ARMANDO TINOCO

BACK-END DEVELOPER

HOW TO COMMUNICATE WITH ME

ajtp18@hotmail.com | (57) 321 6546691 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/armando-tinoco-paternina/

WORK EXPERIENCE CONDOR LABS

Backend Developer | April 2022 - January 2023

- -Development of microservices using REST-type service protocols with JavaScript as programming language and backend-oriented frameworks such as express, Node.JS, Jest for unit tests, among others.
- -Experience with management, edition, and support of relational database search engines such as Oracle SQL, PL/SQL, also non-relational search engines (MONGODB)
- -Use and creation of AWS cloud services through ansible AND PULUMI (TSG, SM, EC2, VPC, AMI)
- -Support of components in production environment through metric analysis, understanding of log files

UNILEVER - ULEX COLOMBIA

Back-end developer | August 2021 - December 2022

- -Responsible for updating and deprecation of articles in app canastto (PYTHON AND SERVERLESS)
- -AWS as database for inventory update.
- Inventory Maintenance (PYTHON, TYPESCRIPT).
- Developer.

EDUCATION

FUNDACION UNIVERSITARIA TECNOLOGICO COMFENALCO.

Profesional - Ingeniería de sistemas| 2022, Actual.

FUNDACION UNIVERSITARIA TECNOLOGICO COMFENALCO.

Tecnologia - Control electronico de procesos | 2017 - 2019

COURSES

Universidad Python, POO, Django, Flask y PostgreSQL, 27 Horas. | 2021.

Python y Flask. Desarollo web y APIS tipo REST con flask, 10.5 Horas | 2021

Node js De cero a experto

React: De cero a experto (Hooks y MERN), (en curso)

EMPLOYMENT AND PERSONAL REFERENCES

request it if necessary